It has now been several years
现在已经好几年了
since the attack by the creatures
自从生物的攻击
that rose from the depths of the ocean
从海洋深处升起
and threatened to destroy all life on earth.
并威胁要摧毁地球上的所有生命。
The death toll was high that day,
当天的死亡人数很多，
particularly on the East Coast of the United States.
特别是在美国的东海岸。
But, thankfully, a team of specially trained pilots
但是，幸好有一支训练有素的飞行员队伍
commandeered the Armada Military Robot Series
征服了Armada军事机器人系列
and went to the battle with the beasts.
并与野兽去战斗。
Those brave soldiers and their massive, high-tech armors
那些勇敢的士兵和他们庞大的高科技装甲
saved the planet from certain destruction.
拯救了这个星球免受某些破坏。
Despite the success of the Armadas,
尽管Armadas的成功，
the destruction is widespread,
破坏很广泛，
and rebuilding the areas hit the hardest has been slow.
重建最困难的地区进展缓慢。
Preventing another such catastrophe is the topic
预防另一场这样的灾难是这个话题
of much heated debate amongst the military,
军方之间激烈的争论，
the State Department, and other national security forces.
国务院和其他国家安全部队。
But rest assured, patrols from the sea, on the land,
但是请放心，从海上巡逻，在陆地上巡逻，
and in the air remain steadfast on preventing
并在空中坚守防范
such a horrible event from occurring again.
这种可怕的事件再次发生。
Nuclear submarines even comb the ocean's floor
核潜艇甚至梳理海底
as a part of the vigilant line of defense.
作为警戒线的一部分。
It's now been years of peace and quiet,
现在已经过了几年的和平与安宁，
and the entire world is about to breathe again.
整个世界即将重新呼吸。
This is Neptune's Nest. Intrepid Gull,
这是海王星的巢穴。 无畏鸥，
do you copy?
你会复制吗？
Yeah, I'm not dead yet.
是的，我还没死。
How's Red Sector today?
红色部门今天如何？
Sonar isn't showing anything right now.
声纳目前没有展示任何东西。
Have you been drinking?
你有一直在喝吗？
I'm retired... sort of.
我退休了......有点。
Have you been running the multiple ray sonar today?
你今天是否在运行多线声纳？
Yeah, a little bit.
是的，一点点。
Hey, you're still on the payroll.
嘿，你还在工资单上。
Yeah, I've been running it every day this week.
是的，这周我每天都在运行它。
Nothing to show.
没什么可显示的。
Hold on a second. I spoke too soon.
稍等一下。 我说得太快了。
I, uh, I got something here. You seeing this?
我，呃，我在这里得到了一些东西。 你看到了吗？
Affirmative, Intrepid Gull.
肯定的，无畏的鸥。
You are to take preemptive measures immediately.
你应该立即采取先发制人的措施。
All right, relax.
好，放松。
Probably just a minor tec drift.
可能只是一个小小的tec漂移。
Depth mines are launched.
深部地雷发射。
First contact in five seconds, four...
第一次接触五秒钟，四...
three...
三...
two...
二...
one.
一。
Contact one,
联系一个，
contact two, three and four.
联系二，三和四。
All charges have made contact.
所有费用都已联系。
Now I'm not showing anything.
现在我没有显示任何东西。
Copy, Intrepid Gull.
复制，无畏鸥。
We're deploying submersibles to investigate.
我们正在部署潜水器进行调查。
What the hell?
我勒个去？
They're back! It's not possible!
他们回来了！ 这不可能！
Intrepid Gull, you're to move two clicks
无畏的鸥，你要移动两次点击
southwest immediately!
西南马上！
I say again, regroup with the flotilla!
我再说一遍，与船队重组！
Copy that.
收到。
No. No, no, no.
没有。 不不不。
Holy shit! What the hell?
神圣的狗屎！ 我勒个去？
Open fire!
开火！
Come on, come on!
好啦好啦！
Main guns, fire!
主炮，火！
Hey, bro, if you need help with the kids,
嗨，兄弟，如果你需要孩子们的帮助，
you and Jenny gotta do it on your own.
你和珍妮必须自己做。
- They're back! - What?
- 他们回来了！ - 什么？
They're back, man!
他们回来了，男人！
You sure?
你确定？
They took down a battleship!
他们拿下了一艘战舰！
It was heading towards shore.
它正朝着岸边驶去。
It's probably there by now.
现在可能已经到了。
I swear, man. We found another one!
我发誓，男人。 我们找到了另一个！
Someone should be rolling up on you in a minute.
有人应该在一分钟内把你卷起来。
It's a guy named Russo.
这是一个名叫Russo的家伙。
I told everyone we were gonna see these things again.
我告诉大家我们会再次看到这些东西。
And I said to we need to update the Armadas from day one!
我说我们需要从第一天开始更新Armadas！
Well, now's your chance.
好吧，现在是你的机会。
Well, here's your boy.
那么，这是你的男孩。
All right. I'll hit you later.
好吧。 我以后会打你。
Got him.
得到了他。
Dr. Roth?
罗斯博士？
My name is Russo, head of the Tactical
我的名字是Russo，战术的负责人
and Security Division of Hallstrom's Labs.
和Hallstrom实验室的安全部门。
We're here to escort you safely to the facility.
我们在这里安全陪伴你到设施。
Yeah, I know.
是的，我知道。
Do you mind if I go grab a change?
你介意我要去换一个改变吗？
We stopped by your house. We have your things.
我们在你家门口停了下来。 我们有你的东西。
They're in the car. Let's go.
他们在车里。 我们走吧。
Let's go, let's go, let's go! We're burning daylight!
走吧，走吧，走吧！ 我们正在燃烧日光！
- ...in some small way. - Whenever you're ready.
-...以一些小的方式。 - 每当你准备好了。
Oh!
哦!
Excuse you! What do you think you're looking at?
原谅你！你认为你在看什么？
I was just being polite.
我只是很有礼貌。
Well, that girl's crushing on you hard, so careful.
那么，那个女孩很难对付你，这么小心。
She's right. She didn't charge you for your drinks.
她是对的。她没有为你的饮料向你收费。
What?
什么？
I'm sure that's not the case.
我相信事实并非如此。
She's new. Maybe she made a mistake.
她是新的。 也许她犯了一个错误。
Right. I'm sure that's what it was.
对。 我确信那就是这样。
- This is on me. - You're damn right it is.
- 这是对我的。 - 你是对的。
Have you guys heard anything about what's going down?
你们有没有听到关于什么事情的消息？
All the higher-ups were a little tense today.
所有的高层今天都有点紧张。
I think I even saw Worthington on the premises.
我想我甚至在场地上看到了沃辛顿。
I don't know, but I heard someone
我不知道，但我听到有人
say they wanna bring in that Dr. Roth guy
说他们想带上那位罗斯博士的家伙
that got fired a while ago.
前一阵子被解雇了。
Dr. Roth? Yeah, that guy's super messed up.
罗斯博士？是的，那家伙的超级搞砸了。
That's why he got fired in the first place.
这就是他为什么首先被解雇的原因。
If you ask me, I think they made a mistake letting him go.
如果你问我，我认为他们犯了一个错误让他离开。
He designed the original OS.
他设计了原始的操作系统。
He's the only one who truly knew the Bots.
他是唯一真正了解机器人的人。
All I know is Horowitz was pissed they were thinking
我所知道的是霍罗威茨生气的时候他们都在想
about bringing in someone else.
关于引进其他人。
Horowitz?
霍洛维茨？
She's super messed up too. Should be fun.
她也超级搞砸了。 应该很有趣。
Tense times.
时态。
Hmmm.
嗯。
That was a risky move. You should be more careful.
这是一个冒险的举动。 你应该更加小心。
And who's winning?
谁赢了？
Oh! He's got no skills!
哦! 他没有技能！
I must have some skills.
我必须有一些技能。
Otherwise, I wouldn't be your squad leader.
否则，我不会成为你的班长。
Between us, I think it's good that
在我们之间，我认为这是好事
they're bringing in some extra help.
他们正在带来一些额外的帮助。
We don't know what's coming,
我们不知道会发生什么，
and if it's anything like last time,
如果它和上次一样，
it's not gonna be a walk in a park.
它不会在公园散步。
They kicked those things' asses last time.
他们上次踢这些东西的屁股。
I say bring it on.
我说带它。
I'm itching for some action too.
我也渴望一些行动。
But what do we really know about these things?
但是我们对这些事情了解多少？
We know they're big giant, ugly-ass motherfuckers,
我们知道他们是巨人，丑陋的混蛋，
and they kill people. What else is there to know?
他们杀人。 还有什么要知道的？
There is this guy at training that said he actually
有这样一个人在训练，他实际上说过
saw one of these things with his own eyes.
亲眼看到了这些东西之一。
Said it was spitting fire.
说这是吐火。
What? Like a dragon?
什么？像龙？
Wait. Don't believe everything you hear, Badger.
等待。不要相信你听到的一切，獾。
Either way, these things are strong.
无论哪种方式，这些东西都很强大。
Probably even stronger than us.
可能比我们还强。
I mean, I can't be the only one who's worried
我的意思是，我不能是唯一担心的人
about these new Bots, new OS, new everything.
关于这些新的机器人，新的操作系统，新的一切。
And the feedback pain?
反馈的痛苦？
If the real deal's anything like what they put us through
如果真正的交易就像他们给我们的东西一样
in simulation, then we are screwed.
在模拟中，然后我们搞砸了。
Oh, babe, afraid of pain?
哦，宝贝，怕疼吗？
No. I'm concerned about performance.
不，我担心表演。
Yeah! Hammer has performance anxiety.
是啊！锤子有表现焦虑。
Seriously.
认真。
I'm willing to do whatever it takes to defend this country,
我愿意尽一切努力来捍卫这个国家，
but I can't be the only one who feels like
但我不能成为唯一一个喜欢的人
we're just not ready.
我们还没有准备好。
You scared?
你害怕？
Yes. You should be, too.
是。 你应该也是。
And we never even got to field test these things.
我们甚至从来没有实地测试过这些东西。
Guys, we've been in the sim so much.
伙计们，我们很喜欢这个模拟器。
If we're not ready now, we're never gonna be.
如果我们现在还没有准备好，我们永远不会。
You don't die in the sim.
你不会在模拟中死亡。
Are you afraid to die?
你害怕死吗？
You can't be if you wanna survive.
如果你想活下去，你不可能成为。
I'm ready to die. Are you?
我准备去死。你是？
Since the day I was born.
自从我出生那天起。
Ooh-rah!
哦-RAH！
You know we really shouldn't be talking about this
你知道我们真的不应该在谈论这个
in a public place.
在公共场所。
She's right.
她是对的。
Most of the time.
大多数时候。
Quit it with that charming shit.
用那个迷人的狗屎放弃它。
What has that ever gotten you?
你曾经得到过什么？
Free drinks.
免费饮料。
You guys think we have time to hit the beach
你们认为我们有时间去海滩
before we have to go back in?
在我们必须回去之前？
Oh, I'm so sick of playing third wheel
噢，我很生病玩三轮
with you two wheelbarrows.
与你两个手推车。
- What does that even mean? - Figure it out.
- 那有什么意思？ - 想办法。
We're awesome.
我们很棒。
What was that?
那是什么？
- They're playing our song. - Let's go.
- 他们正在播放我们的歌曲。 - 我们走吧。
So, catch me up.
所以，赶上我。
The creature made land.
这个生物制造了土地。
We're not sure what it's doing.
我们不确定它在做什么。
It settled down along the shore
它沿着岸边安定下来
and hasn't moved since.
并且从此没有动过。
This is gonna be as bad as it was the first time.
这会和第一次一样糟糕。
Probably worse.
可能更糟糕。
Giant Killer, this is Russo. We're on approach.
巨人杀手，这是俄罗斯人。 我们正在接近。
Giant Killer?
巨人杀手？
Are you comfortable back there?
你在那里舒服吗？
No, not really.
不，不是。
Good.
好。
What the hell is this place?
这个地方到底是什么？
Long ride, huh?
长途骑行，呵？
Personnel on standby.
待命人员。
The facility is 30 stories beneath ground.
该设施在地下30层。
- Hey, Maggie? - Yeah?
- 嘿，玛姬？ - 是吗？
You seeing what I'm seeing?
你看到了我所看到的？
Yeah, and it doesn't look good.
是的，它看起来不太好。
What the...
什么...
Come on, Karen, pick up!
来吧，凯伦，拿起！
Alex, uh... I... I was just about to call you.
亚历克斯，呃......我......我正打算给你打电话。
Listen, get Sam and get out now!
听着，让萨姆出去吧！
I'll meet you at a rendezvous.
我会在会场见面。
I'm seeing something really weird.
我看到一些非常奇怪的东西。
They're back.
他们回来了。
What do you mean, they're back?
你是什么意思，他们回来了？
Karen, where's Sam?
凯伦，山姆在哪里？
She has my car.
她有我的车。
She's gonna pick me up for lunch.
她会去接我吃午饭。
Okay. I'll meet you at the rendezvous.
好的。我会在会场见到你。
Let me know if you can't get her.
如果你找不到她，请告诉我。
I gotta go now. I love you.
我得走了。 我爱你。
Wait...
等待...
Sam, call me as soon as you get this.
山姆，一旦你得到这个，给我打电话。
It's am emergency!
这是紧急情况！
Try to keep up, Mr. Roth.
努力跟上，罗斯先生。
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
Dr. Roth?
罗斯博士？
Thanks for coming out so quickly.
谢谢你这么快出来。
- Did I have a choice? - No.
- 我有选择吗？ - 没有
I'm General Worthington. The Pentagon sent me.
我是沃辛顿将军。 五角大楼派我来了。
The Pentagon?
五角大楼？
This is more of a private facility. Where's Chuck?
这更像是一个私人设施。 Chuck在哪里？
This falls under the Department of Defense.
这属于国防部。
Mr. Rickman will not be present.
里克曼先生将不在场。
Okay.
好的。
Larry Enders tells me you've been caught up
拉里恩德斯告诉我你已经被抓住了
with everything so far. Is that correct?
到目前为止的一切。 那是对的吗？
Yeah, sort of. So what's the deal here?
是的，有点。 那么这里的交易是什么？
The new Bots aren't working like Rickman and Mike
新的机器人不像里克曼和迈克那样工作
and all the other geniuses thought they would?
和所有其他天才认为他们会？
What do you want from me?
你想从我这里得到什么？
You were working on a neural-interface
你正在研究神经接口
with artificial intelligence
与人工智能
without the endurance and transference of pain
没有忍耐和痛苦的转移
from machine to the pilot...
从机器到飞行员...
the problem we had with the last Armada series.
我们在最后一个Armada系列中遇到的问题。
I gave you guys the solutions.
我给你们解决方案。
You didn't wanna use them.
你不想使用它们。
Look, lives are at stake here.
看，这里的生命危在旦夕。
Let's cut past that.
让我们切过去。
Okay. Spinal cord stimulation generator.
好的。脊髓刺激发生器。
It reroutes the sensation of pain from the axon nerves
它改变了轴突神经的疼痛感
and recycles them through the generator in an endless loop.
并通过发电机无限循环地回收它们。
So the pain message never makes it to the brain, essentially.
所以，痛苦的信息从来没有让它进入大脑，本质上。
It sounds easy. It's not.
这听起来很简单。 不是这样。
Let me guess.
让我猜猜。
The DOD's neural transfer link bullshit method
国防部的神经转移链接废话方法
for mitigating pain failed to prove successful,
为了缓解疼痛未能证明成功，
and now you realize that you need to adapt
现在你意识到你需要适应
my neural-transfer link to the Bots' AI system?
我的神经传递链接到机器人的AI系统？
Is that correct, General?
将军是否正确？
Yes, sir. Let me show you something.
是的先生。 让我给你看一些东西。
These are the new Armada Series Military Robots.
这些是新的Armada系列军事机器人。
They're not bad.
他们并不坏。
We need to try your neural-link immediately.
我们需要立即尝试你的神经链接。
Let's do it.
我们开始做吧。
I assume you already have pilots that are trained
我假设你已经有训练有素的飞行员了
to fly these things, right?
飞这些东西吧？
Our pilots have been trained on simulators.
我们的飞行员已经接受过模拟器培训。
But those simulators are operated by
但那些模拟器是由
the old AI software interface.
旧的AI软件界面。
- So never? - Red tape.
- 所以永远不会？ - 繁文缛节。
What else is new?
还有什么是新的？
Dr. Horowitz, the buildings are crumbling like dirt!
霍洛维茨博士，这些建筑物像泥土一样摇摇欲坠！
Are you telling me your Bots are not ready?
你是否告诉我你的机器人还没准备好？
No. No, no, no.
不不不不。
Look, I can assure you that the Armada program
看，我可以向你保证Armada计划
is completely under control, okay?
完全在控制之下，好吗？
I can assure you that Roth nor anyone else is going to be
我可以向你保证，罗斯或其他任何人都不会
a problem, not even the General.
一个问题，甚至不是将军。
Look, Horowitz, with all due respect,
看，霍洛维茨，在所有应有的尊重，
someone with as little experience as you is...
和你一样经验不多的人......
let's just say it's just a tad bit disconcerting.
让我们说这只是一点点令人不安。
I've been in this field for many years now.
我在这个领域已经有很多年了。
I've seen men and women die,
我看到男人和女人死亡，
and I was here the last time these goddamn things
我在这里是最后一次这些该死的事情
killed the people that I love right in front of me!
在我面前杀死了我所爱的人！
Can you say the same for yourself?
你能说一样吗？
Well, then it's all on you.
那么，这一切都在你身上。
Mission accomplished, you'll get a medal.
任务完成后，你将获得一枚奖章。
Mission failure, blood on your hands.
任务失败，血液在你手上。
More blood.
更多的血液。
Mr. Roth has arrived.
罗斯先生已经抵达。
I'll be right there.
我会在那里。
Ah, Dr. Horowitz.
啊，霍洛维茨博士。
Has Naval Command reached you yet?
海军司令部到达了你吗？
No, not yet, Dr. Horowitz. This is Dr. J.P. Roth.
不，还没有，霍洛维茨博士。 这是J.P. Roth博士。
He'll be assisting us for the robotics' neural-interface.
他会帮助我们研究机器人的神经接口。
Nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你。
I know who you are.
我知道你是谁。
I read your theory on quantum interconnectivity, yeah.
我读过你关于量子互连的理论，是的。
I thought it was very well thought out.
我认为这是非常深思熟虑的。
You know, theoretically speaking, of course.
理论上讲，当然你知道。
But would it really work in reality? I don't know.
但它真的能起作用吗？我不知道。
Should I take that as a compliment?
我应该把它当作赞美吗？
Maybe.
也许。
Dr. Roth? Andrus is on a secure line for you.
罗斯博士？安德鲁对你来说是安全的线路。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Hello?
你好？
- You at the labs? - Yeah.
- 你在实验室？ - 是的。
I'm gonna dial in my interface,
我要在我的界面中拨号，
see if I can get these Bots up and running.
看看我能否让这些机器人启动并运行。
Fantastic! Keep me posted!
太棒了！ 让我张贴！
Will do. Hey, take care of yourself.
会做。 嘿，照顾好自己。
You do the same.
你做同样的事。
All right.
好吧。
Dr. Roth? If you will...
罗斯博士？ 如果你愿意......
There she is.
她在这里。
LILAC.
紫丁香。
- Ready to get activated? - Yes, sir.
- 准备好被激活？ - 是的先生。
Ooh! Someone changed the operating system?
哦！有人改变了操作系统？
Yeah. We're on Robonet.
是啊。我们在Robonet。
Are you kidding?
你在开玩笑吗？
My interface was designed to work with Python.
我的界面被设计为与Python一起工作。
What?
什么？
What the...? What was that?
什么......？ 那是什么？
I don't know, but it wasn't good.
我不知道，但它不好。
Mom, I'm stuck in traffic.
妈妈，我被困在交通中。
Sam, I-I need you to pick me up now!
山姆，我 - 我需要你现在接我！
Well, tell that to the idiot causing the traffic.
那么，告诉那些造成交通的白痴。
Okay, well, you need to find a different route.
好吧，你需要找到一条不同的路线。
Wh-what's wrong?
什么是错？
You have five minutes!
你有五分钟！
Five minutes? Mom, I'm gonna have to break a few laws.
5分钟？妈妈，我必须打破一些法律。
Five minutes. Don't stop for anyone or anything.
5分钟。不要停止任何人或任何事情。
Awesome. Wait. This isn't some kind of trick?
真棒。等待。 这不是某种诡计？
I love you. Be safe.
我爱你。注意安全。
Python integrates better with brain mapping.
Python与脑图的整合更好。
I mean, it costs more, a hell of lot more,
我的意思是，它花费更多，更多地狱，
but it's better for the crossover.
但对交叉来说更好。
Robonet's like a dinosaur.
Robonet就像一只恐龙。
Money's not an issue. This is life or death.
钱不是问题。 这是生与死。
Robonet and Python RTC do share some
Robonet和Python RTC确实有一些共同之处
common binary interface, but... one wrong line of code,
常见的二元接口，但是......一行代码错误，
this whole place is gonna blow.
这整个地方都会打击。
Have the pilots been brain-mapped?
飞行员是否被大脑映射？
- They have. - Great.
- 他们有。 - 好极了。
Look, I can only write so much code.
看，我只能写这么多的代码。
Let me see those pilots.
让我看看那些飞行员。
All pilots report to the side room.
所有飞行员都向侧室报告。
I repeat, report to the side room as soon as possible.
我再说一遍，尽快报告给旁边的房间。
Bunch of kids.
一群孩子。
I hope I don't fry their brains.
我希望我不要炒作他们的大脑。
They've had training, Doc.
他们接受过培训，Doc。
What's going on, Doc? Why aren't the Bots responding?
怎么回事，Doc？ 为什么不是机器人响应？
That lag.
那个滞后。
I can't fix the lag without overhauling the entire software.
如果不修整整个软件，我无法修复延迟。
There's no time for that, Doctor!
医生没时间了！
These pilots are highly trained.
这些飞行员训练有素。
They'll be able to compensate.
他们将能够赔偿。
I'm not sending these pilots up there
我不是在那里派这些飞行员
to their death without control of their Bots!
到他们的死亡没有控制他们的机器人！
Do you get it?
你明白吗？
My name is Hammer, sir.
先生，我叫Hammer。
I knew the risks when I signed up for the job.
当我报名参加工作时，我知道风险。
They need us out there.
他们需要我们在那里。
Do you understand the problem we have here, Hammer?
你明白我们在这里的问题吗，哈默？
You have a lag.
你有滞后。
That's a delayed response in your brain's motor impulse
这是对你的大脑运动冲动的延迟反应
to the Bot's AI system.
到Bot的AI系统。
You'll never see a strike. You see?
你永远不会看到罢工。 你看？
If you had a lag, you never would have seen that coming.
如果你有滞后，你永远不会看到这种情况。
I appreciate your concern, sir.
先生，我很感谢你的关心。
We all do.
大家都这样做。
It's all we got, Doc.
这是我们得到的，Doc。
I lost my family to those things three years ago.
三年前我失去了我的家庭。
Please, let us do our jobs.
请让我们做好我们的工作。
All right, rig 'em up.
好吧，装备好吧。
Mom?
妈妈？
Out! I'm driving.
出来了！我在开车。
What? What's going on?
什么？到底是怎么回事？
We have to get out of town.
我们必须离开城镇。
What about work? Where's Dad?
工作怎么样？ 爸爸在哪里？
He's gonna meet us at grandma's house.
他会在奶奶家和我们见面。
In Tennessee? Out there?
在田纳西州？ 在那里？
This must be bad.
这一定是不好的。
Okay, who's ready?
好的，谁准备好了？
- Ready, sir. - Have a seat.
- 准备好了，先生。 - 坐下。
Mr. Hammer, you're gonna feel a small shock.
哈默先生，你会感到一阵小小的震惊。
It will subside after a moment.
一会儿它会消退。
Initializing.
初始化。
Activating.
激活。
Yes, sir. Felt that.
是的先生。感觉。
His head's all ready. Next victim, please.
他的头都准备好了。 拜托下一位受害者。
- Call sign "Bugs," sir. - Bugs?
- 呼号“虫虫”，先生。 - 虫虫？
- Sting like a bee... - That's original. Sit down.
- 像蜜蜂一样刺痛... - 那是原创的。坐下。
- Initializing. - I got it.
- 初始化。 - 我知道了。
Activating.
激活。
Stung you?
蜇你？
I can handle it.
我应付得来。
Okay. Next victim.
好的。下一个受害者
Call sign "Badger," sir.
呼号“Badger”，先生。
Have a seat.
请坐。
- Initializing. - Activating.
- 初始化。 - 激活。
- Feels good. - Feels good. Okay.
- 感觉不错。 - 感觉不错。好的。
We're all set.
我们都准备好了。
So, we're ready to test them out?
那么，我们准备好测试它们了吗？
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
You heard the man. Climb into your Armada.
你听到了那个人。 爬进你的舰队。
Yes, sir!
是的先生！
All right, let's lock and load! Let's go!
好吧，让我们锁定并加载！我们走吧！
You heard the man!
你听到了那个男人！
Let's go, let's go! We ain't got time!
走吧，走吧！ 我们没有时间！
Their exoskeletons have calcified exponentially,
他们的外骨骼呈指数级钙化，
presumably due to the increased temperature in the core.
据推测是由于核心温度升高。
Blaming it on global warming?
把它归咎于全球变暖？
Bone density isn't singular like a normal organism.
骨密度并不像正常的生物体那样单一。
It's layered.
它是分层的。
Compared to the last ones,
与最后一个相比，
these ones are making them look like crickets.
这些让他们看起来像蟋蟀。
This hedomorph is truly an incredible creature.
这hedomorph是一个真正令人难以置信的生物。
What is it with you?
你怎么样？
What?
什么？
I don't know. You seem to admire these things.
我不知道。 你似乎很欣赏这些东西。
I'm studying the physical form of an unknown alien species.
我正在研究一种未知的外来物种的物理形态。
These hedomorphs have killed millions of people, okay?
这些hedomorphs已经杀死了数百万人，好吗？
Forgive me if I'm not fascinated.
如果我没有着迷，请原谅我。
Yeah, and you need to understand your enemy
是的，你需要了解你的敌人
in order to defeat them.
以打败他们。
I know enough.
我足够了解。
Why are you even here?
你为什么在这里？
I was looking for an LDO to add
我正在寻找一个LDO来添加
to the Bots' matrix interface,
到机器人的矩阵界面，
but apparently they have changed everything.
但显然他们已经改变了一切。
Why an LDO? What would that do?
为什么选择LDO？ 那会做什么？
It'll help with the respond to the RR and with compliance.
它将有助于回应RR和合规。
Not by much, but at this point, I'll take what we can get.
不是太多，但在这一点上，我会拿我们能得到的。
Mm.
毫米。
Now General Worthington,
沃辛顿将军，
he seems pretty willing to sacrifice his pilots.
他似乎很愿意牺牲他的飞行员。
You know him better than I do.
你比他更了解他。
Can we trust him not to push them too far?
我们能相信他不要把他们推得太远吗？
No, he knows what they're capable of.
不，他知道他们有能力。
I wouldn't underestimate them.
我不会低估他们。
They're tougher than you think.
他们比你想象的更强硬。
This is not about being tough.
这不是艰难的。
When you link into the Bots' matrix,
当你连接到机器人的矩阵时，
it's a whole other level of strength that's required.
这是需要的整个其他水平的力量。
And I know these Armadas better than anyone else.
而且我比其他人更了解这些Armadas。
You did.
你做到了。
Been out of the game for a while now, Roth.
罗斯已经离开了一段时间的比赛。
I noticed. I spent years
我注意到。我花了几年时间
coding and programming these things to a T.
编码和编程这些东西到一个T.
I come back, and there's Mickey Mouse code on it.
我回来了，它上面有米老鼠的代码。
Listen, I know it doesn't look like it used to.
听着，我知道它看起来不像以前那样。
But we've made considerable progress.
但我们已经取得了很大的进展。
The Armadas are the best they're gonna be.
Armadas是他们最好的。
Obviously not.
很明显不是。
Otherwise they wouldn't have brought me back.
否则他们不会把我带回来。
I'm linked in.
我被链接进去了。
Okay, Hammer, when you move, don't just physically move.
好的，锤子，当你移动时，不要只是身体移动。
I want you to consciously concentrate on the movement.
我希望你有意识地专注于运动。
The neural-interface will work faster
神经接口将工作得更快
with your brain motor impulse.
用你的脑电机冲动。
Make sense?
合理？
I think so.
我想是这样。
Okay.
好的。
Now you need to get a grasp on the delay time, okay?
现在你需要掌握延迟时间，好吗？
Bugs and Badger, you do the same.
臭虫和獾，你也这样做。
Come up with a movement for your Bot.
为您的Bot创建一个动作。
- Copy.
- 复制。
Keep working with it.
继续使用它。
You guys have to compensate for the lag time.
你们必须补偿滞后时间。
It's the only thing that's gonna save your life out there.
这是唯一能拯救你生命的东西。
Okay, let's check on your weapons systems now.
好的，现在我们来看看你的武器系统。
All right! Party time.
好吧！ 晚会时间。
There's no delay in the weapons system.
武器系统没有延迟。
We have that going for us. Pilots!
我们已经为我们做了。 飞行员！
Begin prep and final diagnostics!
开始准备和最终诊断！
The creature is holding its position,
该生物正在保持其位置，
and we are still unsure of its intentions,
我们仍然不确定其意图，
but it's causing mass destruction
但它正在造成大规模破坏
and we need to get you into the field.
我们需要让你进入这个领域。
Begin initial on sequence.
从序列开始初始化。
- Roger. - Copy.
- 罗杰。 - 复制。
Retract orbital arms.
撤回轨道武器。
Main engines start.
主引擎启动。
Copy that.
收到。
Ready to launch. I say again, ready to launch.
准备发射。 我再说一次，准备发射。
We're clear to lift off.
我们很清楚要起飞。
All right!
好吧！
Engage boosters.
参与助推器。
Mom, I'm scared!
妈妈，我很害怕！
It's okay. It's going to be okay.
没关系。 它会好起来的。
We just need to get out of town.
我们只需要出城。
Mom, watch out!
妈妈，小心！
Mom, we're gonna die here.
妈妈，我们会死在这里。
Sam, we have to stay calm.
山姆，我们必须保持冷静。
Everyone's getting out of their car!
每个人都离开他们的车！
To where? We have to stay here.
去哪里？ 我们必须留在这里。
And get crushed like a bug? No! We're leaving!
像虫子一样被粉碎？ 没有！我们走了！
Sam... Damn it.
山姆......该死的。
Sam!
山姆！
We're still a couple of miles out from the contact.
我们离联系人还有几英里远。
How's everybody doing?
大家好吗？
Helm is a little slow to respond, but I can deal.
头盔有点慢，但我可以处理。
This Bot is barely responsive.
这个机器人几乎没有反应。
Yeah.
是啊。
Let's get a little practice in along the way,
让我们一起练习一下，
work out all the kinks now before we engage this thing.
在我们搞这个事情之前，先解决所有的问题。
You guys getting the hang of the lag time?
你们得到了滞后时间的悬念？
Affirmative, sir.
肯定的，先生。
It's taking some getting used to,
它正在采取一些习惯，
but we'll be okay.
但我们会好起来的。
Bugs? Badger?
错误？獾？
- Yeah, I'm good, sir. - Same.
- 是的，我很好，先生。 - 相同。
Giant Killer, we have visual on the bogey.
巨人杀手，我们有视觉上的忌酒。
I say again, we have visual on the bogey.
我再说一遍，我们有视觉上的忌酒。
And it's a lot bigger than I thought.
这比我想象的要大得多。
General, this lag time is gonna kill 'em.
一般来说，这个滞后时间会杀死他们。
You really want them operating without full control?
你真的希望他们没有完全控制的操作？
They'll be fine, Dr. Roth.
他们会没事的，罗斯博士。
Giant Killer?
巨人杀手？
Awaiting instructions, Giant Killer.
等待指示，巨人杀手。
You are clear to engage, Hammer!
你很清楚，哈默！
I say again, you are clear to engage!
我再说一遍，你很清楚要参与进来！
You heard the man. We're clear to engage.
你听到了那个人。 我们很清楚要参与。
Roger.
罗杰。
Solid copy.
坚实的副本。
Badger, Bugs, cover me. I'm sending in rockets.
獾，虫虫，掩护我。 我正在发射火箭。
Copy that.
收到。
Bam!
巴姆！
Giant Killer? Direct hit on bogey.
巨人杀手？ 直接袭击柏忌。
I say again, direct hit!
我再说一遍，直接命中！
Good job, Hammer!
干得好，锤子！
Can you confirm the creature is deceased?
你能证实这个生物已经死亡吗？
We'll move in for a closer look, Giant Killer.
我们将进一步看看，巨人杀手。
- Did you guys see that? - Yeah.
- 你们看到了吗？ - 是的。
What does that mean?
那是什么意思？
It's not dead, guys!
它没死，伙计们！
Giant killer! The bogey is not deceased!
巨人杀手！ 柏忌不是已故的！
I say again, it is not deceased.
我再说一遍，它并没有死亡。
This thing is getting slower and slower!
这件事变得越来越慢！
I've... I've got a problem.
我...我有一个问题。
My control panel is shorting out.
我的控制面板正在短路。
I think I'm losing power.
我想我失去了力量。
Is that Dad?
那是爸爸吗？
What just happened?
刚刚发生了什么？
Giant Killer?
巨人杀手？
- Sam... - Is it over?
- 山姆... - 结束了吗？
Sam, we need to go! We need to go!
山姆，我们需要走了！ 我们需要去！
Guys! Guys! Guys!
伙计们！伙计们！伙计们！
I need... I need help!
我需要......我需要帮助！
I need... I need your help!
我需要... 我需要你的帮助！
I'm having a hard time breathing.
我呼吸困难。
We've lost radio contact with Armada One!
我们失去了无线电与Armada One的联系！
It's shutting down, going off-line!
它正在关闭，离线！
Life support is failing!
生命支持失败！
I can't do anything from here.
我无法从这里做任何事情。
I have to get out there. It's not a system error!
我必须走出去。 这不是系统错误！
It's a physical problem aboard the Bot!
这是Bot上的一个物理问题！
Hammer, what's going on in there?
锤子，那里发生了什么？
Hang on, Hammer!
等一下，锤子！
I'm coming, Hammer!
我来了，锤子！
Bugs, watch out!
错误，小心！
Yeah, yeah, I know.
是的，是的，我知道。
Bugs, stay on this thing!
虫虫，留在这个东西！
I'm gonna go and cover Hammer!
我要去掩护锤子！
General, I have to get out there, please! Right now!
一般，我必须走出去，请！马上！
Russo.
鲁索。
Lee, Wright. Let's go! Let's boogie!
李，赖特。我们走吧！ 我们来布吉吧！
Dr. Horowitz, I need one of you to stay here.
霍洛维茨博士，我需要你们中的一个留在这里。
- Hey! - Doctor!
- 嘿！ - 医生！
Sorry, Doctor. We can't let you do that.
对不起，医生。 我们不能让你这样做。
It's too dangerous.
这太危险了。
I did a four-year residency in a trauma ward.
我在创伤病房做了四年的住院治疗。
We do not have time for this shit.
我们没有时间去做这件事。
- We need to go. - Hammer needs me there.
- 我们需要走。 - 锤子需要我在那里。
I'll shadow her, Russo.
我会影响她，Russo。
But stay close.
但保持关闭。
Let's go!
我们走吧！
You okay in there, Bugs?
你没事吧，虫子？
Yeah, I'm good.
是的，我很好。
Holy cow.
天啊。
That's all right, we'll be fine.
没关系，我们会好起来的。
Almost there.
差不多了。
Son of a...
的儿子...
Shit!
拉屎！
Stay calm, Doctor, stay calm.
保持冷静，医生，保持冷静。
Oh, my God.
哦，我的上帝。
I didn't know they made them that big.
我不知道他们让他们变得如此之大。
It's crazy.
这太疯狂了。
Hit the gas!
打气！
We're all right. Almost there. Easy.
我们没事。 差不多了。简单。
How's our six doing, Wright?
赖特，我们的六个人怎么样？
Wright, you're on six.
赖特，你六点了。
Look, look! Hold on, hold on. You can see air.
看看！等一下，等一下。 你可以看到空气。
What?
什么？
Air coming out of his cockpit.
空气从他的驾驶舱出来。
That's the oxygen supply.
这是氧气供应。
How do we fix it?
我们如何解决它？
These robots, they're equipped with
这些机器人，他们配备
tank units, just like spacecraft.
坦克单位，就像航天器一样。
The impact from the attack probably knocked out
攻击的影响可能会被打破
the filtration, right?
过滤，对吧？
So we have to seal the valve.
所以我们必须密封阀门。
So what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna try to salvage
所以我要做的是我会尽力打捞
the ECU to get the Armada back online.
ECU让Armada重新联机。
Okay, you do that. I'm gonna take care of Hammer.
好的，你这样做。 我会照顾锤子。
Damn it, Bugs! Shoot the damn thing!
该死的，臭虫！ 拍摄该死的东西！
You're too close for the missile.
你对这枚导弹来说太近了。
I'm gonna have to use the Gatling.
我将不得不使用加特林。
That's fine. Just do something!
没事儿。 只要做点事情！
Engaging the Gatling guns.
使用Gatling枪。
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
简单，轻松，简单，轻松。
- Yes, sir. - Lee?
- 是的先生。 - 李？
- I'm on it, Russo. - Hold it down.
- 我在上面，Russo。 - 按住不放。
I'm going up.
我正在上升。
Hammer!
锤子！
No response.
没有反应。
The cockpit is filled with gas.
驾驶舱内充满了气体。
We have to get Hammer out of there.
我们必须让Hammer离开那里。
Roth, you too.
罗斯，你也是。
Hammer.
锤子。
- Hammer! - Oh, my God.
- 锤子！ - 哦，我的上帝。
Hammer!
锤子！
- I got it, go fix the ECU. - I'm on it!
- 我知道了，去修理ECU。 - 我去做！
- Stay with me, please. - Hang in there, baby.
- 请跟我来。 - 挂在那里，宝贝。
- Look at me. - Come on!
- 看着我。 - 来吧！
Hammer!
锤子！
I don't have a pulse. Get my medical bag!
我没有脉搏。 拿我的医疗包！
Hang on, buddy.
等一下，哥们。
Hang on. Don't you give up.
不挂断。你不放弃吗？
- We got you! - Come on, man!
- 我们抓到你了！ - 来吧，伙计！
Roth! It's getting real hard to breathe!
罗斯！呼吸真的很难！
Stay with us!
和我们在一起！
- Come on! - Don't you give up now.
- 来吧！ - 你现在不放弃吗？
Stay with me.
跟我在一起。
Come on!
来吧！
Come on.
来吧。
Hammer, come on.
锤子，来吧。
- We took too long. - God damn it!
- 我们花了太长时间。 - 他妈的！
He's dead. He's dead. We gotta go.
他死了。 他死了。我们要走了。
We'll take him with us. We can't just leave him.
我们会带他走。 我们不能离开他。
We don't got time! We gotta go,
我们没有时间！ 我们要走了，
or we're all gonna suffocate.
或者我们都会窒息而死。
Go, go!
去吧，去吧！
I'll stay and clean up.
我会留下并清理。
The entire human species working together
整个人类一起工作
couldn't take this thing out.
不能把这件事拿出来。
Damn it, Bugs! What in the hell are you doing?
该死的，臭虫！ 你到底在做什么？
Badger, use your missiles!
獾，使用你的导弹！
Negative! It's too risky!
负！ 这太冒险了！
Release it!
释放它！
You have a clear shot!
你有一个清晰的镜头！
Blow this son of a bitch away!
吹这个婊子的儿子！
I can't hold onto him forever!
我无法永远拥抱他！
Missiles away!
导弹离开！
Disengage!
松开！
Take cover! Take cover! Take cover!
采取掩护！采取掩护！ 采取掩护！
The creature is down!
这个生物已经灭绝了！
I say again, the creature is down!
我再说一遍，这个生物已经灭绝了！
Giant Killer, copy!
巨人杀手，复制！
We have visual confirmation.
我们有视觉确认。
Good work, Mr. Russo.
Russo先生，祝你工作顺利。
What's the status on Hammer?
Hammer的状态如何？
Mr. Russo, where is Hammer?
鲁索先生，锤子在哪里？
I say again, where is Hammer?
我再说一次，锤子在哪里？
Where's Hammer?
锤子在哪里？
He's dead.
他死了。
What?
什么？
No!
没有！
Damn!
该死的！
All right, I gotta get a closer look.
好的，我得仔细看看。
No, no, no.
不不不。
Look! Look, I have to get closer, okay?
看！看，我必须靠近，好吗？
If there are more things out there like this,
如果像这样有更多的东西在那里，
I have to learn everything I can!
我必须尽我所能去学习！
You are killing me.
你要杀死我了。
Bugs and Badger, Bugs and Badger, this is Russo.
臭虫和獾，臭虫和獾，这是Russo。
ASAP, ASAP, I need overview.
尽快，尽快，我需要概述。
Copy, Giant Killer!
复制，巨人杀手！
Copy.
复制。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
This doesn't... This doesn't look good.
这不... 这看起来不太好。
- Run! - This doesn't look good.
- 跑！ - 这看起来不太好。
- Go, go, go! - Fall back!
- 冲啊！ - 倒退！
- Take cover, go! - Go, go, go!
- 保护，去吧！ - 冲啊！
Fall back! Cover, cover, cover! Fall in! Fall in!
倒退！封面，封面，封面！落入！落入！
Armada, Armada, multiple hostile movers!
舰队，舰队，多个敌对行动者！
No! No!
没有！没有！
Ah!
啊!
Bugs, Badger, hold fire!
虫虫，獾，抓住火！
Abort, abort!
中止，放弃！
Copy, Giant Killer.
复制，巨人杀手。
Bugs, where are you?
虫虫，你在哪里？
I'm here!
我在这里！
All right.
好吧。
Returning to base!
回到基地！
Oh, God! Okay.
天啊！好的。
Alex? Alex?
亚历克斯？亚历克斯？
- Karen? - Are you okay?
- 凯伦？ - 你还好吗？
Look, I'm fine.
看，我很好。
Karen, are you out of the city?
凯伦，你离开这个城市吗？
No.
没有。
We're looking for a pheno-bunker.
我们正在寻找一个地堡。
Are you still driving?
你还在开车吗？
No, we had to go on foot.
不，我们必须步行。
Karen, no! You cannot be on foot!
凯伦，不！ 你不能徒步！
I mean, we're okay for the moment.
我的意思是，我们现在还好。
It got really quiet. Did you guys kill it?
它变得非常安静。 你们杀了它吗？
You need to get off the streets!
你需要走出街头！
Mom...
妈妈...
Find a room, lock yourselves in there now!
找到一个房间，现在就锁定在那里！
- I'll come for you. - Okay...
- 我会来找你的。 - 好的...
- Mom! - What?
- 妈妈！ - 什么？
Shit, shit!
屎，狗屎！
Karen!
卡伦！
Damn it!
该死的！
We'll reorganize,
我们将重新组织，
mobilize ground troops.
动员地面部队。
We'll send the Armadas back out as overwatch.
我们会将Armadas作为守望派退出。
The ground troops can go building to building,
地面部队可以去建筑物，
street to street to clear the insects.
街道到街道清理昆虫。
We can't let them get too far inland.
我们不能让他们走得太远。
We'll never be able to contain them.
我们将永远无法包含它们。
Negative. Absolutely not.
负。 绝对不。
No, that means way too many casualties, General.
不，那意味着伤亡太多，将军。
Civilians are bound to get caught up in the crossfire.
平民一定会卷入交火。
It's too risky.
这太冒险了。
We're moving to Phase Two.
我们正在进入第二阶段。
Copy.
复制。
We'll implement Phase Two.
我们将实施第二阶段。
Anyone care to tell me what Phase Two is?
任何人都在意告诉我第二阶段是什么？
It's me, Dr. Roth.
是我，罗斯博士。
Bioweapons.
生物武器。
You gotta be kidding me.
你得开玩笑吧。
Biological warfare?
生物战？
You can't come up with another alternative?
你不能拿出另一种选择？
Like send in an air strike or something?
像发送空袭或什么？
We did that. It didn't work.
我们做到了。 它没有工作。
Well, whatever the hell you're gonna use,
那么，无论你将要使用什么，
it's gonna go everywhere.
它会到处去。
You're talking about a major fallout.
你正在谈论一个重大的后果。
Dr. Roth, I'm not gonna drop a carpet bomb, okay?
罗斯博士，我不会放下地毯炸弹，好吗？
I'm gonna target the creatures specifically.
我将专门针对这些生物。
The Armadas are back.
Armadas又回来了。
What is it that you require, Dr. Horowitz,
霍洛维茨博士说，你需要什么？
to begin Phase Two?
开始第二阶段？
I'm gonna need one of the spiders.
我需要蜘蛛之一。
I need to know what we're dealing with.
我需要知道我们正在处理的是什么。
I don't care what the U.N. thinks.
我不在乎联合国的想法。
Pull it up.
把它拉起来。
I'm sorry, sir. We did what we could.
先生，我很抱歉。 我们尽我们所能。
Yeah. I mean... you did.
是啊。 我的意思是......你做到了。
You did what you could.
你做了你能做的。
We're gonna move forward with Phase Two now.
我们现在要继续前进第二阶段。
Get some rest until you're needed again.
休息一下，直到你再次需要。
Badger, keep an eye on her, will you?
獾，注意她，是吗？
Will do, sir.
会的，先生。
Get yourself checked out by a medic.
让医生检查一下。
I need a perimeter set around the outskirts of town.
我需要一个围绕城镇郊区的周边。
I want anything with more than two legs killed on sight!
我希望有任何两只以上的腿在视线中死亡的东西！
Copy.
复制。
Prepared to do anything?
准备做任何事情？
We both are.
我们都是。
We need you.
我们需要你。
You understand the robots better than anyone else,
你比任何人都更了解机器人，
and that's exactly why you're here.
这正是你来到这里的原因。
But you need to learn how to follow the rules,
但是你需要学习如何遵守规则，
and I make the rules.
我制定规则。
How is it that you make the rules about
你是如何制定规则的？
what the Armadas can and cannot do
Armadas可以做什么，不可以做什么
when you yourself admit that I know more about them?
当你自己承认我更了解他们？
Yes, but you're skeptical.
是的，但你是怀疑的。
You're full of doubt.
你充满怀疑。
And I know that those robots are more capable than you think.
而且我知道那些机器人比你想象的更有能力。
They could have been if Hallstrom
如果是Hallstrom，他们本来可以
had let me finish my work.
让我完成了我的工作。
Hey, I completely agree with you, okay?
嘿，我完全同意你，好吗？
And on a separate note, I admit, you know,
另外，我承认，你知道，
you're not who I expected you to be either.
你不是我所期望的你。
Did you say something nice to me?
你对我说了些好话吗？
I'm just saying I'm sorry that I misjudged you
我只是说我很抱歉，我误判了你
- when I first met you. - You misjudged me?
- 当我第一次见到你时。 - 你错误地判断了我？
With all due respect, you do carry a certain reputation.
在所有应有的尊重下，你确实拥有一定的声誉。
I do?
我做？
You threw a chair out the window.
你把椅子扔出窗外。
Yeah.
是啊。
I need to know, if I can synthesize a targeted bioweapon,
我需要知道，如果我能合成一个有针对性的生物武器，
would you be able to reformat the Armadas
你能够重新格式化Armadas吗？
and disperse everything effectively?
并有效地分散一切？
I would have to expend the resonance
我将不得不消耗共鸣
to amplify the power output. But, yes, it's doable.
放大功率输出。 但是，是的，这是可行的。
Good.
好。
Lee, ridge.
李，山脊。
On it.
在上面。
What are we doing here?
我们在这里做什么？
Planning an ambush.
计划伏击。
We gotta get a vantage point on those damn spiders,
我们必须在那些该死的蜘蛛身上获得有利位置，
figure out where they're at.
找出他们在哪里。
Where they're grouping, where they're going to.
他们在哪里分组，他们要去哪里。
Get the stragglers and the weak ones.
得到落后者和弱者。
How about you?
你呢？
How'd you end up running this team?
你最终怎么运行这个团队？
Uh...
呃...
My team was attacked by these things near San Diego.
我的团队在圣地亚哥附近遭到这些事件的袭击。
I'd been appointed to the DOD
我会被任命为国防部
on scientific special operations.
科学的特殊行动。
My people died because I hesitated on utilizing
我的人因为犹豫利用而死亡
human assets in a war we were already losing.
战争中的人力资产我们已经失败。
I said retreat when I should have said attack.
我说应该说我的攻击时会退缩。
I was the only survivor that day.
那天我是唯一的幸存者。
It made be a bit of an expert with DIA, DOD and POTUS.
它成为DIA，DOD和POTUS的专家。
We understand risk, Roth.
我们了解风险，罗斯。
It's all we have left.
这是我们所有的一切。
How's it looking?
它看起来如何？
They're staying together offshore
他们在一起离岸
but we got a few small groups that are breaking off
但是我们有几个小组正在脱离
and they are headed into town.
他们进入城镇。
We're gonna get a little company.
我们会得到一个小公司。
It's gonna heat up here pretty quick, guys!
它会在这里变得很快，伙计们！
Let's go ahead and get doctors back to lab!
让我们继续，让医生回到实验室！
Copy that.
收到。
I'm not going back in.
我不回去了。
Absolutely not.
绝对不。
It's way too dangerous out there.
那里太危险了。
They're everywhere.
他们无处不在。
We'll get you your spider.
我们会让你的蜘蛛。
Back to the lab. Let's go.
回到实验室。 我们走吧。
And what if you can't get a spider back to the lab?
如果你不能让蜘蛛回到实验室呢？
What if I need to take a tissue sample from the field?
如果我需要从野外采集组织样本怎么办？
Are you familiar with taking tissue samples
你对组织样本很熟悉吗？
from the field and gathering them yourself, Mr. Russo?
Russo先生，从现场收集它们吗？
Lee, Wright. Check that.
李，赖特。 检查一下。
We'll take Dr. Roth back to lab,
我们会让罗斯博士回到实验室，
and we will head back out.
我们将退出。
No, I'm not going anywhere.
不，我不会去任何地方。
It's a waste of valuable time.
这是浪费宝贵的时间。
Besides, I could stay here and help out Horowitz.
此外，我可以留在这里帮助霍洛维茨。
There! There!
那里！那里！
Mom! Mom!
妈妈！妈妈！
Sam, run! Run!
山姆，跑吧！跑！
Go! Go!
走！走！
Okay, okay.
好吧好吧。
Mom?
妈妈？
It's okay. We just...
没关系。我们刚刚...
We just need to find a locked room.
我们只需要找到一个锁定的房间。
Come on!
来吧！
Russo!
鲁索！
I got activity in front of that house.
我在那所房子前面有活动。
I don't like this.
我不喜欢这个。
- Easy! Easy! - I got 'em!
- 简单！简单！ - 我得到了他们！
- Stand down. - I can take 'em!
- 站起来。 - 我可以拿他们的！
Stand down!
站起来！
Whoa!
哇！
We do not have the firepower or the manpower
我们没有火力或人力
to take these things on in numbers.
把这些东西在数量上。
They're tearing this guy up, you kidding me?
他们在撕裂这个人，你在开玩笑吗？
Anything happens to you or Dr. Horowitz,
任何事情发生在你或霍洛维茨博士身上，
this mission is a failure.
这个使命是失败的。
Our best shot is to get one of these spiders alone,
我们最好的办法是单独获得这些蜘蛛之一，
preferably dead.
最好是死的。
We can't get into a firefight with these things in numbers.
我们无法用数字来解决这些问题。
Look!
看！
- Wright, stay with 'em. - Got it.
- 赖特，和他们在一起。 - 得到它了。
- Lee, stay tight. - On you.
- 李，保持紧张。 - 在你身上。
- Lee. - I see 'em.
- 李。 - 我看到他们。
- I got one by itself. - Got two to the left!
- 我自己得到了一个。 - 左边有两个！
On my five!
在我的五个！
Three, one!
三，一个！
Help! We need help!
帮帮我！ 我们需要帮助！
- On it! - Wright!
- 在上面！ - 赖特！
What happened?
发生了什么？
Roth! Roth! Get back here!
罗斯！罗斯！ 回到这里！
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Russo! Wright is down! Roth is coming to you!
鲁索！赖特倒了！ 罗斯来找你！
How'd you learn to shoot like that?
你怎么学会像那样拍摄？
I'm from New York.
我来自纽约。
Come on. Let's bag this thing up.
来吧。 让我们把这件东西包起来。
In the back.
在后面。
Move!
移动！
Go! Go!
走！走！
Okay. We'll be okay.
好的。 我们会没事的。
What if those weird spider things get in here?
如果那些奇怪的蜘蛛事物进入这里怎么办？
Or another like monster comes and destroys this building?
或者另一个像怪物来破坏这个建筑？
Sam?
萨姆？
Sam, we're not gonna freak out, okay?
山姆，我们不会吓坏了，好吗？
Look at me. Take a breath.
看着我。 喘口气。
Okay.
好的。
Your father's gonna find us, okay?
你父亲会找到我们的，好吗？
Got it?
得到它了？
I'm gonna apply a little bit of pressure.
我会施加一点压力。
It might sting a little bit.
它可能会刺痛一点点。
- Bring it on. - Relax.
- 来吧。 - 放松。
Relax? Hammer is dead!
放松？ 锤子死了！
We need to get back out there...
我们需要回到那里...
You need to calm down!
你需要冷静下来！
I'd really recommend you relax for a day or two.
我真的会建议你放松一两天。
To hell with that.
与此同时。
I need to get back out there now!
我现在需要回到那里！
Are the Bots ready?
机器人准备好了吗？
We'll have our chance.
我们有机会。
He's dead.
他死了。
I want them dead.
我想让他们死。
We knew what we signed up for.
我们知道我们注册了什么。
I just can't believe he's gone.
我简直不敢相信他走了。
I'm not gonna cry.
我不会哭的。
Let me take another look.
让我再看一看。
No. I need to go now.
不，我现在得走了。
I can't release you.
我无法释放你。
I'm not asking you.
我不是问你。
Then you're gonna have to sign some paperwork.
那么你将不得不签署一些文书工作。
Where's the damn pen?
该死的笔在哪里？
Doc.
文档。
On three, on three.
三，三。
One, two, three.
一二三。
Easy, easy, easy, easy, easy.
轻松，简单，轻松，简单，轻松。
Okay. Drop it, guys. Drop it.
好的。放下吧，伙计们。 算了吧。
No, we gotta leave it outside.
不，我们得把它留在外面。
We still don't know if this thing's giving anything off.
我们仍然不知道这件事是否放弃了。
I don't want to contaminate the facility.
我不想污染设施。
Let's just bring all my equipment out here.
让我们把所有的装备都带到这里。
All right, got it. On three, on three.
好的，明白了。 三，三。
Three, two.
三，二。
This is Russo, this is Russo.
这是Russo，这是Russo。
I need you to bring down Dr. Horowitz's equipment ASAP.
我需要你尽快降低Horowitz博士的设备。
Repeat?
重复？
You gotta be kidding me.
你得开玩笑吧。
- Really? - Copy.
- 真的吗？ - 复制。
You've got a phone call.
你有电话。
I just lost a friend to one of these things. Make it quick.
我刚刚失去了一个朋友，其中一件事。快一点。
Hello?
你好？
Larry, where the hell are you, man?
拉里，你在哪里，男人？
I'm on the way back in.
我正在回来的路上。
Listen, man, before that boat went down,
听着，男人，在那艘船停下来之前，
we got a definite area on where those things are coming from.
我们在这些事情的来源方面得到了一个明确的领域。
But we got an attack sub out here ready to go nuclear
但是我们在这里得到了一个攻击准备好去核
and blow these things out!
并吹掉这些东西！
Do you have any idea how big the tidal waves
你有什么想法有多大的浪潮
that thing would create?
那件事会创造？
I get it, I get it.
我明白了，我明白了。
All right, what else do you have?
好的，你还有什么？
There's much more, a whole lot more.
还有更多，还有更多。
There's fucking more of these things?
他妈的更多这些东西？
Yeah, well, you're the one who predicted it, right?
是的，你是预言者，对吧？
I wish I was wrong about that one.
我希望我对那个错了。
I know, but what are you guys doing about these spiders?
我知道，但你们对这些蜘蛛做了什么？
And what about the Armada?
那么Armada呢？
We nabbed one of the spiders.
我们抓住了一只蜘蛛。
Horowitz is trying to figure out a pathogen
霍罗威茨试图找出病原体
to kill these things off, and I'm gonna figure out a way
杀掉这些东西，我会找出一个办法
to adapt it to the Armadas and deploy it.
以适应Armadas并部署它。
Sounds like a plan.
听起来像是个计划。
All right, I'll keep you posted as I know it.
好吧，我会保持你张贴，因为我知道它。
Great. Glad you're alive.
大。 很高兴你还活着。
Me, too.
我也是。
You done?
你完成了吗？
There's more?
还有更多？
Yeah.
是啊。
What do you think?
你怎么看？
I think they look like ordinary arachnids, you know.
你知道，我认为他们看起来像普通的蜘蛛。
With the exception to their size, of course.
当然，除了它们的大小之外。
That could be due to radiation or, you know,
这可能是由于辐射，或者你知道，
we just discovered a new species.
我们刚刚发现了一个新物种。
I won't know anything for sure until I cut that thing open.
除非我把这件事情打开，否则我无法确定任何事情。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Mr. Secretary, I understand nobody was prepared.
秘书先生，我知道没有人准备好。
Yeah, okay.
好的。
Look, if you need to mobilize more ground troops, then do it!
看，如果你需要动员更多的地面部队，那么就做吧！
General, Dr. Horowitz's equipment is set up, sir.
一般来说，霍洛维茨博士的设备已经建好了，先生。
Copy.
复制。
Hmm.
嗯。
Let's see.
让我们来看看。
Okay, so radiation levels seem to be normal
好吧，辐射水平似乎是正常的
and it's not emitting any kind of toxins either.
它也不会释放任何毒素。
Well, that's good news.
那么，这是个好消息。
All right, so let's take a look inside you.
好的，让我们来看看你的内心。
That thing stinks.
那东西很臭。
Huh. Well, this is interesting.
呵呵。那么，这很有趣。
There are definitely organs I can't identify here.
这里有一些我无法辨认的器官。
I mean, usually with these things, you can figure them out
我的意思是，通常用这些东西，你可以把它们弄清楚
if you have a general working knowledge of
如果你有一般的工作知识
how the organism works, but this...
生物体如何工作，但是这...
Guys, this isn't carbon-based.
伙计们，这不是以碳为基础的。
All life on earth is carbon-based.
地球上的所有生命都是以碳为基础的。
What are you saying, Doctor?
你在说什么，医生？
These things are not from earth?
这些东西不是来自地球？
Whoa.
哇。
So if these things aren't from earth, then they're aliens.
所以如果这些东西不是来自地球，那么它们就是外星人。
Well, if you have another hypothesis,
那么，如果你有另一个假设，
- I would love to hear it. - Come on.
- 我很乐意听到它。 - 来吧。
Regardless whether they're aliens,
无论他们是外星人，
the issue at hand is stopping these things!
目前的问题是阻止这些事情！
Of course, General.
当然，一般。
Keep me informed, please.
请告知我。
I need to update the White House on our progress.
我需要根据我们的进展更新白宫。
Okay, so you see this gland here?
好吧，你在这里看到这个腺体？
Yeah.
是啊。
So usually this would be used to expel salt
所以通常这将用于驱逐盐
from the body, right?
从身体上，对吧？
But it seems to be covered with to what I can only refer to
但它似乎已经涵盖了我只能提及的内容
as some sort of reverse plasma membrane.
作为某种逆转质膜。
- It's like crystallized salt. - Yes.
- 它就像结晶盐。 - 是的。
This organ is definitely storing salt.
这个器官肯定是储存盐。
Which actually would make a lot of sense
这实际上会有很大的意义
because the reverse plasma membranes are probably
因为逆转的质膜很可能
drawing in sodium from the ocean in which it's living in.
从它所居住的海洋中吸取钠。
It's being stored in its glands
它被储存在它的腺体中
and it's rereleasing it back into its system,
并将其重新发回到其系统中，
just like our body does with insulin.
就像我们的身体与胰岛素一样。
Kind of like camels storing fat in its hump?
有点像骆驼储存脂肪的驼峰？
Right. That's a good analogy.
对。 这是一个很好的比喻。
This is good news because if I can find a way
这是个好消息，因为如果我能找到一个方法
to actually destroy these membranes,
实际上破坏这些膜，
it would be a much better alternative than creating
这将比创建更好
a pathogen that would actually pollute the environment
一种实际上会污染环境的病原体
and run the risk of hurting the population.
并冒着伤害人口的风险。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
This is Intrepid Gull,
这是“无畏鸥”，
closing in on the new sonar activity.
关闭新的声纳活动。
Guys, I think there is something else under here!
伙计们，我认为这里还有别的东西！
I'm outta here.
我在这里失控。
Come on, baby, come on.
来吧，宝贝，来吧。
Come on!
来吧！
Come on, keep it going. Keep it going.
来吧，继续下去。 保持下去。
Come on, let's go.
来吧，走吧。
Ah!
啊!
The U.S.S. Radiant is closing in on the location
美国联合航空Radiant 正在关闭位置
the Intrepid Gull locked on before it was destroyed.
无畏鸥在它被摧毁之前锁定。
The nuclear weapons are armed.
核武器是武装的。
Maybe this could be the way out.
也许这可能是出路。
You know what I think.
你知道我的想法。
Atlantic Command, this is Commanding Officer Sterling
大西洋司令部，这是英镑指挥官
of the U.S.S. Radiant.
美国联邦统计局辐射。的
You seeing these images?
你看到这些图像？
Atlantic Command. Affirmative, Radiant.
大西洋司令部。 肯定的，光芒四射。
You are clear to sweep and destroy.
你清楚地清扫和摧毁。
I say again, you're clear
我再说一遍，你很清楚要扫除和摧毁。
Copy that, Atlantic Command.
复制一下，大西洋司令部。
Complying with orders to sweep and destroy.
遵守清扫和摧毁的命令。
Forward torpedo room, I need tubes one through four
向前的鱼雷室，我需要一到四个管
ready to go with MOD7 CBASS immediately.
准备立即与MOD7 CBASS一起使用。
Copy, Command. MOD7 CBASS, copy.
复制，命令。 MOD7 CBASS，复制。
Prepare for launch on my mark.
准备在我的商标上发布。
And three... two...
还有三个......两个......
one, mark!
一，马克！
Or not.
或不。
You gotta be kidding me.
你得开玩笑吧。
It was destroyed.
它被毁坏了。
There's another creature out there.
那里还有另一个生物。
Creatures.
生物。
I need to know if Dr. Horowitz has figured out a way
我需要知道霍洛维茨博士是否已经找到了一种方法
to destroy these things.
摧毁这些东西。
And I need those Armadas right now!
我现在需要那些Armadas！
Copy.
复制。
And that is how we kill them.
这就是我们如何杀死他们。
The spiders are okay.
蜘蛛是好的。
But what's the possibility we have another larger creature?
但有什么可能我们有另一个更大的生物？
Well, I mean, my assumption is since the spiders came
我的意思是，我的假设是蜘蛛来了以后
from the larger creature in the first place,
从更大的生物首先，
they probably share the same genetic makeup and organs,
他们可能共享相同的基因构成和器官，
so I don't see why they wouldn't.
所以我不明白他们为什么不会。
The Armadas will be the best option
Armadas将是最好的选择
for deploying this agent.
用于部署此代理。
Do you agree?
你同意吗？
Absolutely.
绝对。
But how do we deploy this?
但我们如何部署这个？
- The flame units. - Hmm, brilliant.
- 火焰单位。 - 嗯，很棒。
I just have to tweak them a bit.
我只需要稍微调整一下。
Okay. Let's get on it ASAP.
好的。 让我们尽快完成。
Keep us apprised, Doctor. We don't have much time.
让我们知道，博士。 我们没有太多时间。
No time, for that matter.
没有时间，就此而言。
You sure this is gonna work?
你确定这会工作？
It's all we've got.
这是我们所有的。
Is that what you're looking for?
那是你在找什么？
Yeah.
是啊。
We could use a bigger one...
我们可以使用一个更大的...
22 or 24... but it'll do for now.
22或24... 但它现在会做。
Okay.
好的。
Hey...
嘿...
Thank you for working with me.
感谢你和我一起工作。
I'm glad we got to work together.
我很高兴我们能够一起工作。
Even if it's the last day we're alive.
即使这是我们活着的最后一天。
Okay, Mr. Russo.
好的，Russo先生。
Let me know when you see the igniter light go out.
当你看到点火器灯熄灭时让我知道。
All right, it's off!
好吧，它已经关闭了！
Aerial and naval surveillance have just confirmed
空中和海军监视已经确认
two bogies moving toward shore.
两个转向岸的转向架。
Two?
二？
Jesus!
耶稣！
Like a glove.
像手套一样。
That should do it. Locked and loaded!
这应该做到这一点。 锁定并加载！
I suggest that we keep one as a backup.
我建议我们保留一个作为备份。
That sounds good to me.
这听起来不错。
Very well.
很好。
So is it ready?
那准备好了吗？
As ready as it's gonna be.
准备就绪，因为它会是。
Where's the pilots?
飞行员在哪里？
I can't stand this waiting around stuff.
我受不了这个等待的东西。
It drives me nuts.
它使我疯狂。
Bugs? Badger?
错误？獾？
Need you down in the hangar ASAP!
需要你尽快在机库里！
Finally!
最后！
Bugs, wake up. It's time to go.
错误，醒来。 现在是时候了。
Bugs, get your ass up! It's time to go!
虫虫，让你的屁股！ 现在是时候了！
Bugs!
错误！
Oh my God!
哦，我的上帝！
Russo!
鲁索！
Bugs, Badger, I need you down here ASAP, ASAP!
虫子，獾，我需要你在这里尽快，尽快！
Russo, you need to get down here!
Russo，你需要在这里下车！
There's something wrong with Bugs!
Bug有错误！
I turned her around and she's like...
我转过身来，她就像......
What the hell?
我勒个去？
Russo, why won't the door open?
Russo，为什么不开门？
I am losing good men right now!
我现在失去了好人！
What the hell is going on?!
这到底是怎么回事？！
We have to quarantine them.
我们必须隔离它们。
We're not letting them out of there.
我们不会让他们离开那里。
- She caught a contagion. - All right.
- 她感染了传染病。 - 好吧。
If we don't have any pilots to fly the Armadas,
如果我们没有任何飞行员驾驶Armadas，
how are we gonna stop these things?
我们将如何阻止这些事情？
Wait.
等待。
Do you mean to tell me, General,
你的意思是告诉我，将军，
that we don't have any pilots left?
我们没有任何飞行员离开？
We do, but not at this location.
我们这样做，但不在这个位置。
I mean, this was all so sudden.
我的意思是，这一切都很突然。
We were extremely unprepared.
我们非常措手不及。
It's gotta be me.
它必须是我。
Doc, can anybody get into those damn things?
医生，有人可以进入那些该死的东西吗？
Are you brain-mapped?
你是脑图吗？
No. That is why I'm asking.
不，那是我问的原因。
Yes, you do.
是的你是。
We can outfit you with Bugs's rig,
我们可以用Bugs的钻机来装备你，
but the lag time will be even greater.
但滞后时间会更长。
Everyone's brain mapping is slightly different
每个人的大脑映射都略有不同
and I have no idea how the Armada's gonna work for you.
我不知道Armada如何为你工作。
We have no other choice.
我们别无选择。
Put me in the damn thing. Just put me in there.
把我放在该死的东西。 只要把我放在那里。
I'll take the other one.
我会拿另一个。
No. I need you to stay down here and watch my back, okay?
不，我需要你留下来看我的背，好吗？
No, I'm gonna pilot the other Armada.
不，我要试驾其他舰队。
I cannot put you in control of
我不能让你控制
a billion dollar robot, Doctor.
十亿美元的机器人博士。
General, the Armada's AI works off of our brain impulse.
一般来说，Armada的人工智能可以消除我们的大脑冲动。
I'm already brain-mapped.
我已经大脑映射。
I have the least amount of lag time.
我有最少的延迟时间。
No.
没有。
Quite frankly, we have no other choice!
坦率地说，我们别无选择！
We can't send this man up alone.
我们不能单独派这个人。
No. Let someone else do it.
不，让别人去做吧。
You worried about me, Horowitz?
你担心我，霍洛维茨？
Maybe...
也许...
And it's Andrea.
这是安德烈。
J.P.
J.P。
What's that stand for?
这是什么意思？
If I come back alive, I'll let you know.
如果我活着回来，我会让你知道的。
Then come back alive.
然后活着回来。
Kill them.
杀了他们。
- So you guys are ready? - All set.
- 所以你们准备好了？ - 可以了，好了。
Let's go, let's go, let's go! Let's suit up!
走吧，走吧，走吧！让我们穿上吧！
Lee, are you in position?
李，你有位置吗？
Affirmative. I have eyes on the target.
肯定。 我有目标的眼睛。
Roger. ETA two minutes.
罗杰。 ETA两分钟。
Copy that.
收到。
Make sure the targets are tagged
确保目标被标记
before we get there.
在我们到达那里之前。
Russo, change your L sat to 070328!
Russo，把你的L换成070328！
Standing by for activation.
等待激活。
Got it. Signal loud and clear.
得到它了。 信号响亮而清晰。
This should make it easier
这应该会更容易
for the missiles to hit the target.
导弹击中目标。
Go get 'em, Russo.
去拿他们，Russo。
Doc, make sure you stay behind me!
医生，确保你留在我身后！
I'll take the brunt of all the attacks!
我将首先承受所有的攻击！
When I give the word, you go ahead
当我说出这个词时，你就继续前进
and deploy the aerosol attack! You got that?
并部署气溶胶攻击！ 你明白了吗？
Will do.
会做。
Are you seeing what we're seeing down here?
你看到我们在这里看到什么了吗？
Wow! What the hell are they doing?
哇！他们到底在做什么？
All the spiders are attaching themselves
所有的蜘蛛都附着在身上
to a larger creature.
到更大的生物。
All right now, stay back. Don't get eager.
现在好了，留下来。不要急于求成。
Let me take the pass first, and we'll see how they react.
让我先通过，然后我们会看到他们的反应。
Russo. watch out!
鲁索。小心！
The big one is going for you!
最重要的是为你而去！
I'm coming in, Russo!
我来了，俄罗斯！
Negative! Stay back!
负！留下来！
Mr. Russo, you've got a lot of spiders
鲁索先生，你有很多蜘蛛
headed your way!
朝你的方向走去！
Yeah. Yeah, I know, Doc.
是啊。是的，我知道，Doc。
But this damn AI, serious lag, serious lag.
但是这个该死的AI，严重滞后，严重滞后。
God, it's like moving through mud!
上帝，就像穿过泥土！
Just say the word!
只要说出这个词！
Now! Deploy it now!
现在！现在部署它！
Okay, I'm there!
好吧，我在那里！
What? What? It's not working!
什么？什么？ 它不工作！
Doc, you're clear to use the flamethrower!
Doc，你很清楚使用火焰喷射器！
Use the damn flamethrower!
使用该死的喷火器！
It's not working!
它不工作！
The flamethrower's down!
喷火器掉了！
Doc, move!
医生，搬家！
Oh!
哦!
Ah!
啊!
Thank you.
谢谢。
Have you figured out
你有没有想过
what's wrong with the weapon system yet?
武器系统有什么问题呢？
No.
没有。
No, it's still down!
不，它仍然下降！
Well, you gotta stay clear
那么，你必须保持清醒
until you figure out how to fix it!
直到你找出如何解决它！
Agh!
哎！
Damn it!
该死的！
All right, I am low on ammo. I am low on ammo.
好，我的弹药很低。 我的弹药很低。
Fall back while using the rockets.
在使用火箭时后退。
Stay at a safe distance.
保持安全的距离。
I repeat, stay at a safe distance!
我再说一遍，保持安全距离！
Copy that?
收到？
Gotcha.
疑难杂症。
Come on, let's go! Come on!
来吧，走吧！ 来吧！
Yeah! Come on!
是啊！来吧！
Let's go!
我们走吧！
How are we going on the flamethrower, Doc?
Doc，我们怎么去喷火器？
Nothing is working.
没有任何工作。
I don't know if it's going to happen.
我不知道这是否会发生。
Fix that damn flamethrower! Put it online!
修复那该死的火焰喷射器！ 把它放在网上！
We gotta get that damn thing online!
我们必须在网上获得该死的东西！
Oh, for... Please tell me you're seeing this.
哦，因为...请告诉我你看到了这个。
Yes.
是。
Giant Killer, are you getting this feed?
巨人杀手，你得到这个饲料？
Yes, Mr. Russo! We see it!
是的，鲁索先生！ 我们看到它！
It looks like they're killing each other.
看起来他们正在互相残杀。
What the hell is it?
这到底是什么？
Roth, what you thinking?
罗斯，你在想什么？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
It's recombining.
它正在重组。
What the hell does that mean?
这到底意味着什么？
It's got recombinant proteins.
它有重组蛋白。
It's becoming one organism.
它正在变成一个有机体。
I think you're right.
我想你是对的。
Dr. Roth, get back!
罗斯博士，回来！
Get back!
回来！
Doc, I need you to stay as far back from this thing
医生，我需要你远离这件事
as possible until you figure out what the hell
尽可能直到你弄清楚到底是什么
is going on with that weapons system!
正在使用那个武器系统！
You copy that?
你复制那个？
Yeah, yeah, I do, Mr. Russo.
是的，是的，我是，鲁索先生。
Dr. Roth, have you figured another way
罗斯博士，你有没有想过另一种方式
to release the pathogens yet?
释放病原体呢？
No, not yet.
还没有。
Give me the backup canister. I'm going out there.
给我备份罐。 我要去那里。
No, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不。
You're not going out there alone.
你不会一个人去那里。
That's suicide.
那是自杀。
I'm going.
我要去。
All right, I'll go with you. I'll escort you.
好吧，我会和你一起去的。 我会护送你。
I'll keep you safe. You're getting back.
我会保证你的安全。 你回来了。
Okay?
好的？
Protect her, Lee. She's our last resort.
保护她，李。 她是我们的最后一招。
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
Come on.
来吧。
Move!
移动！
My leg! It's burning through!
我的腿！它正在燃烧！
It's burning through the suit.
它穿着西装燃烧。
Please tell me you got it online!
请告诉我你已经在线！
Tell me you got the weapons back online.
告诉我你把武器拿回来了。
Negative, but I have an idea!
消极，但我有一个主意！
I'm gonna jam this flamethrower's arm
我要堵住这个喷火器的手臂
down this thing's neck.
放下这件事的脖子。
The acid should eat its way through the fuselage
酸应该穿过机身
and release the aerosol.
并释放气溶胶。
That's crazy, Roth. That's crazy.
罗斯，这太疯狂了。 这很疯狂。
All right.
好吧。
I got it, I got it, I got an idea.
我明白了，我明白了，我有一个主意。
Hold up, guys!
抱起来，伙计们！
No need for the backup canister just yet.
现在不需要备份容器。
Let me try this first.
让我先试试这个。
Roth, are you sure?
罗斯，你确定？
I don't like this.
我不喜欢这个。
This thing is way too strong.
这件事太强大了。
You might want to consider weakening it first.
你可能想先考虑削弱它。
And how do you suggest we do this?
你如何建议我们这样做？
Missiles aren't exactly accomplishing that,
导弹并不完全是这样做的，
and I don't know what will.
我不知道会发生什么。
I know what will do it,
我知道会做什么，
just gotta be direct and precise.
只需要直接和精确。
Russo, I don't like that tone.
Russo，我不喜欢那种口气。
That's what you said in Tripoli, man.
那是你在的黎波里所说的，男人。
- What is it? - Karen.
- 它是什么？ - 凯伦。
Your wife?
你妻子？
Yeah, looks like she's in a building
是的，看起来她正在建筑物中
half a mile away from here.
离这里半英里远。
Let's go get her.
我们去找她吧。
No, we need to be Roth and Russo's backup.
不，我们需要成为罗斯和俄罗斯的替补。
Lee, we got this. Go get your wife and daughter.
李，我们得到了这个。 去找你的妻子和女儿。
Here's what we gotta do first.
这是我们首先要做的。
I'm gonna ram into that son of a bitch,
我会撞见那个婊子的儿子，
and then you gotta finish the job.
然后你必须完成这项工作。
That's not necessary, Russo.
Russo没有必要。
Just hang in there. I'm coming in!
只要挂在那里。 我来了！
Shut up!
闭嘴！
Just do what the hell I'm telling you!
只要做到底我在告诉你！
Go on my signal, on my signal.
根据我的信号继续我的信号。
Ready?
准备？
Okay. Here we go.
好的。 开始了。
Russo, no!
Russo，不！
That's all you got? Huh?
这就是你得到的一切？咦？
Two...
二...
No!
没有！
What was that?
那是什么？
Shh, shh, shh.
嘘，嘘，嘘。
I love you, sweetheart.
我爱你亲爱的。
I love you, too.
我也爱你。
Karen?
卡伦？
Dad! I knew you'd come!
爸！ 我知道你会来！
Alex.
亚历克斯。
I knew you'd come.
我知道你会来。
Is it over?
结束了吗？
Yeah.
是啊。
I have a car outside. Let's go home.
外面有一辆车。 我们回家吧。
Okay, I'm gonna ram this down its throat.
好吧，我要把它压在喉咙里。
Come on, baby! Use your acid.
来吧宝贝！ 使用你的酸。
All right, come to mama!
好，来妈妈吧！
Ugh!
啊!
Are they both okay?
他们都好吗？
Safe and sound. Thank you for that, Doctor.
安然无恙。 谢谢你，博士。
Okay, now we need to get to Roth
好的，现在我们需要去罗斯
before the acid eats through his cockpit.
酸在他的驾驶舱吃完之前。
Hang on, Doc. This could get squirrely.
等一下，Doc。 这可能会变得很棘手。
Here, take a right.
在这里，采取一个权利。
Doc, get Roth. I'll cover you from here.
医生，让罗斯。 我会在这里掩护你。
Dr. Roth?
罗斯博士？
Can you hear me?
你能听到我吗？
Dr. Roth, can you hear me?
罗斯医生，你能听到我吗？
Oh, fuck.
哦，他妈的。
Can you...
你可以吗...
Hey, it's me. It's Andrea.
嘿，这是我。 这是安德烈。
What happened?
发生了什么？
You killed them. That's what happened.
你杀了他们。 这就是发生了什么事。
You're a hero.
你是英雄。
We got to get you out of here, okay?
我们必须让你离开这里，好吗？
Okay, come on. Come on.
好的，来吧。 来吧。
You're okay.
你没事。
Come on, we gotta go quick. Come on.
来吧，我们得快点。 来吧。
Let's go, let's go.
走吧，走吧。
James Patrick.
James Patrick。
What?
什么？
That's my name.
这是我的名字。
I told you I'd tell you if I made it out alive.
我告诉过你，如果我活着出来，我会告诉你。
Well, James, I'm glad you're not dead.
詹姆斯，我很高兴你没死。
Me, too.
我也是。